http://www.acns.org/privacy-policy

Home
About ACNSMission, Vision & Strategic PlanHistoryGovernanceExecutive OfficeMembershipBecome an ACNS MemberMember TypesMembership BenefitsMembership FAQsMember DirectoryUpdate Member ProfileEducationOnline LearningIn-Service Exam in Clinical NeurophysiologyProgram Director ResourcesTrainee ResourcesFeatured CaseMeetingsAnnual Meeting and CoursesFall CoursesFuture MeetingsPast MeetingsEndorsed Courses & SymposiaPracticeCOVID-19 ResourcesGuidelines and Consensus StatementsPractice-Related Resources (Members Only)Coding and Reimbursement (Members Only)ResearchSupport for Clinical Research ConsortiaCritical Care EEG Monitoring Research Consortium (CCEMRC)HD-EEG ConsortiumStereo EEG ConsortiumPublicationsJournal of Clinical NeurophysiologyClinical Neurophysiology NewsAdvocacyFederal Policy AgendaACNS Policy PrioritiesGuidelines and Consensus StatementsCoding & ReimbursementRelationships to Other Related OrganizationsGet InvolvedMembers OnlyProfileMember DirectoryAsk ACNS
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
The American Clinical Neurophysiology Society (ACNS) has a strong commitment to privacy. This statement outlines the policies and procedures concerning information gathering and dissemination practices related to www.acns.org, as well as member, meeting attendee, and sponsor/supporter (collectively, “users”) data. This policy is in accordance with the European General Data Protection Regulations (GDPR).
Collection of User Information
ACNS collects information from individuals who access its website or otherwise interact with the Society.
ACNS uses forms, both web-based and hardcopy, by which members/customers (users) may request information, products, and services. Order forms are used to collect users information closely related to the requested information, product or service, including, but not limited to:
Contact information (e.g., name, address, phone number, e-mail address, etc);
Demographic information;
Practice information; and
Financial information (e.g., account or credit card numbers).
Information collected via these forms relates closely and directly to the information, product, or service requested by the user.
ACNS may also use cookies (a small data file that can be placed on your hard drive when you visit certain websites) to collect, store, and sometimes track information related to use of the ACNS website.
Use and Disclosure of Personal Information
Information collected via the methods outlined above is used to provide a customized experience as you use the ACNS website or participate in ACNS products and services. User information collected via forms and cookies is used for statistical purposes, to deliver or improve the products and services we provide, or to save your settings and to provide customizable and personalized services.
Financial information is used to bill the user for products and services and then is deleted from our records in compliance with the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI-DSS). Contact information from the order form is used to send orders, contact the user regarding any problems with the order, and to provide the user with information about our association, including promotional materials.
It is the policy of ACNS not to share this information with third parties. Exceptions to this policy include disclosure of personal information collected if we have a legitimate business interest in doing so, have received your permission in advance, or in very special circumstances, such as when we believe that such disclosure is required by law, or in other special cases described below.
ACNS may disclose personal information about users, or information regarding your use of our site, for any reason if, in our sole discretion, we believe that it is reasonable to do so, including: to satisfy laws, such as the Electronic Communications Privacy Act, regulations, or governmental or legal requests for such information; to disclose information that is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating our user policies; to operate the site properly; or to protect ACNS and our users.
Use of ACNS website cookies do not enable third parties to access any of your personal information. Third parties and other non-ACNS websites may also use their own cookies. We do not control use of these cookies and expressly disclaim responsibility for information collected through them. Cookies are used to support Google Analytics functionality for website activity tracking. Google Analytics stores information at Google. View details regarding Google Analytics privacy and security.
Membership Directory
Current ACNS members' contact information is made available through the Member Directory. This information is only available to other current ACNS members. Members may opt out of being listed in the Member Directory; see the Updating User Profile section below.
Updating User Profile
Individuals who have created an account with ACNS have the ability to update or change all personal information provided. To do so, users may visit the My Profile section of the ACNS website, or email the ACNS Executive Office (info@acns.org) with updated information.
Opt In/Out of Communications
It is the policy of ACNS not to use or share the personal information about users in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.
ACNS provides individuals the opportunity to opt out of receiving communications from us when we request information about the user. To update these preferences, users may visit the ACNS website or email the ACNS Executive Office (info@acns.org).
ACNS also allows our members to opt out of displaying personal information in the Membership Directory. To update these preferences, members may visit the ACNS website or email the ACNS Executive Office (info@acns.org).
Security
Our site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control, but we cannot guarantee that our security measures will prevent third-party "hackers" from illegally obtaining this information.
Links to Other Sites
This site contains links to other sites. ACNS is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of other websites. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of each website that collects your personally identifiable information.
Changes to This Policy
ACNS reserves the right to revise, amend, or modify this Privacy Policy and our other policies and agreements at any time and in any manner. Notice of any revision, amendment, or modification will be posted.
Last updated: September 20, 2018
American Clinical Neurophysiology Society
555 E. Wells St., Suite 1100   Milwaukee, WI 53202-3823
Phone: (414) 918-9803 | Fax: 414-276-3349 | info@acns.org
© 2001-2020 American Clinical Neurophysiology Society (ACNS)
